The next day
Good morning
Bye, All the best!
We had a lot of ideas until now
We are going to show the officialJosh
River
From this week, we'll test the vlogs
First, let's decide who will go first.
Rock, paper, scissors.
The winner will decide who goes first.
I'll go first.
Okay, I'll go first.
Okay, you go first.
Okay.
Next, Kami.
By the way, I'll decide who goes first.
Okay.
I have a lot of cards.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I'll go first.
I have a lot of cards.
Okay.
I'll go first.
Tantei.
Oh.
I'll explain what this is.
There are members who do other fake
projects.
That's a fake shoot.
Fake shoot.
They just shoot.
They just do it.
They are told to take a treasure.
Fake shoot.
They can't take the treasure.
If they take it, it's bad.
They don't know that and get fooled.
They get fooled and take the treasure.
If they take it, it's a fake shoot.
They put it on and try to take it.
They get arrested.
If they don't have confidence, they
can't take it.
If they take it, they get arrested.
That's the plan.
Tantei.
Tantei shouldn't come to the back.
They shouldn't be on the camera.
Because Tantei should wear navy suits,
short sleeves, red tie, and black
glasses.
That's good.
Oh.
I'll go next.
Do you have a plan?
The first one is related to the name.
It's a beautiful name.
It's a name of a soy sauce crab.
It sounds interesting.
Thank you for watching.
The project I want to do is...
Marumaru Kikuteisen!
I was wondering who should be the
member of Marumaru.
Should I choose a member or a different
person?
So, where are we going now?
Budokan!
Yes!
To go to the Japanese Budokan, we need
to be known more.
There are many people who are watching
YouTube and who haven't seen it yet.
We need to be seen by them.
That means we need to understand you.
I see.
So, the person I want to choose is...
Mina-san...
Kikuteisen!
The members will answer this question.
For example,
what is the ratio of male and female
fans?
I see.
It's not a specific ratio.
What is the ratio of male and female
fans?
For example,
Kikuteisen!
Then, what kind of content should we
show to women?
I see.
I want a smaller one.
So, I need to choose a smaller one.
It's like a present.
It's a present.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
To go to the Japanese Budokan, we need
to understand you and get more support.
So, I suggest you to choose Kikuteisen!
Great!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Can you show us one more item?
Sure.
Let's go one by one.
I have another one.
It's this.
Don't look at it.
He said don't look at it.
It's a white rice and a flare-up.
That's great.
White rice is a white flare-up.
That's right.
We need to heal ourselves on a daily
basis.
We don't have many opportunities to eat
white rice.
We want to use the power of YouTube and
the power of Inari-Gundan to interact
with white rice.
For the viewers, the collaboration
between cute members and cute white rice
is very...
It's a big deal.
So, we need it.
I think there are many.
It's very healing.
It's very healing for the viewers.
I recommend this.
I agree.
Let's clap.
I think it's good to have something
like that sometimes.
Please.
Please subscribe to our channel.
The second thing I'm worried about
is...
First of all, we did a concert the
other day.
I was on the same team as Shinju and
Miyu.
I'm afraid the paint didn't go well.
Miyu was sent to a room despite the
name Lucky Fujitani.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a shocker, so I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to Lucky.
That's why I came up with this idea.
Do you think it's Fujitani?
It's not Fujitani.
Some of you may not know the theory
that RUNE's theory is correct.
In RUNE's case, we're going to guess
what the other members thought of.
It's a very funny project.
I like it. I'm good at it.
I'm good at it.
It's Miyu's version.
But Miyu isn't a poem.
I don't usually say poems.
What I'm going to do is...
I'm going to show you a gag.
I'm going to show you a gag that Miyu
thought of and a gag that someone else
thought of.
The members will guess which one is
Miyu's gag.
It's natural that they know Miyu.
So I'm going to suggest a project that
it's either Miyu or Miyu.
I want to do it.
I've been thinking about a lot of
ideas.
I asked Miyu if I could suggest a gag.
She said, do it right now.
So I did it right now.
I've never seen Miyu's gag before.
I don't know much about the subject.
I only know about the subject.
It's a project to test the good
relationship between Miyu and us.
It's like this.
It sounds fun.
I want to do it.
The members will guess Miyu's gag.
There are four.
I think we can do everything.
I'm going to talk about which one is
better.
In the opinion of adults,
Miyu's gag is the best.
The presence of the president's family.
This hair..
Today's present is...
Their love for each other didn't last.
I'm so happy!
But I don't think you can make all of
them.
I think you can make all of them.
I want to do this!
It was a pain to prepare the white
rice, wasn't it?
I don't know anyone who knows about
white rice.
Right?
So I want to do this.
Nami's is realistic.
The main character looks interesting.
Shinju is also there.
So I want to do this.
I want to do this.
You can make all of them.
And you can't say anything interesting.
I see.
It's a real project.
If you say a gag, we can shoot it in 30
minutes.
You said it immediately.
I said, what?
I said, are you eating?
You said it at once.
I can't say that we will do this.
We will do it alternately.
We will see the thumbnail of the white
rice, the judge, the number, or the
funny Lucky.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to wear a tool.
White rice.
It's blue rice.
Poor thing.
I want to ask other members.
Please explain the project.
Please subscribe to the channel.
The last one?
I want to do trampoline.
I'll write it down.
I've been saying this before I started
YouTube.
Take me to trampoline.
If the project presented behind the
video is realized,
we may upload the video.
Please look forward to it.
That's all for today.
See you.
Bye.
If you want to be on YouTube,
please write a comment.
I want to be on YouTube.
I'm waiting for you.
Thank you for watching this video.